Yosi Cohen, welcome to Honestly.
>> Thank you very much for having me.
>> Well, a lot of people on the internet
believe that you are my boss because
they believe that I am a member of the
Mossad, but this is actually the first
time that I'm meeting you or at least as
far as I know any member of the Mossad.
So, I'm very excited to meet you.
>> I'm the first one you've ever met, but
you know,
>> there might be I might have met people.
>> There might be others that you know the
world.
>> First, I want to set the table for
people because the Mossad is an agency
that is just shrouded in so much
conspiracy and propaganda. Simple
question, Yosi. What is the MOSAD?
>> Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Tim
Dylan Show. Uh, a friend of the show,
Barry Weiss, did a fascinating interview
with a member of the MSAD
and she really looked into
the process and it was incredibly
interesting. So what I want to do now is
I wanted to bring someone in to explore
an area where I am completely clueless.
I mean completely in the dark and I
wanted somebody to kind of walk me
through uh an area of study that I know
nothing about just like Barry did. Uh so
I want to thank you for coming Chloe.
You work at Dairy Queen.
>> That is true. Yes.
What is Dairy Queen
in your mind? What is it? Because people
say that they serve ice cream there and
I'm not even I'm not even super sure
what that is.
>> What's ice cream?
>> Yeah. What is ice cream?
Like what is it?
>> Oh, um it's like a the frozen dessert
ice cream.
>> A like a little treat. It is. It is a
treat. Yeah.
>> Uh like a frozen kind of a It's an like
an ice.
>> It can It's sweet. It's uh It can be
soft or hard. It's uh chocolate,
vanilla.
>> And those are
>> those are the flavors.
>> Flavors.
>> Yeah.
>> So there's different flavors of ice
cream.
>> There's many flavors of ice cream.
>> So that So that's something interesting
to know too. There's
>> Sure. Yeah. Now, what is Dairy Queen to
ice cream? What do they do?
>> Dairy Queen, it's um it's a pretty
popular franchise here in America. I'm
pretty sure it's global actually.
>> So, it's an ice cream store.
>> Sure. Yeah, we're we're known for that.
Um we also sell like burgers and uh
>> So, if I wanted to, I could get ice
cream at Dairy Queen.
>> Yes.
What would be uh some of the ice cream
varieties of D? What's a fun thing
people like there?
>> You know, uh some people just get the
vanilla classic. We do something called
the Blizzard.
>> Now, what is that?
>> That I'm surprised you don't A lot of
people know about the Blizzard. It's um
weard
>> upside down. Have you seen that?
>> Does it involve candy?
There's chopped candies in it,
>> right?
>> Yeah.
>> This is ringing a bell to me now. And
they go in the ice cream.
>> We mix it in.
>> You mix the candy and the ice cream. And
then I I if I wanted to could buy cuz I
wanted to have someone on cuz I don't
know what this is.
>> This ice cream and candy and the ice
cream at this Dairy Queen. What is it?
And so many people are curious about it.
I don't know anything about it. I've
never had it, been near it, gone near
it. Don't think I've ever met anyone
who's had ice cream or even worked in an
ice cream store. So, for someone like
you to come in, again, me knowing
absolutely nothing about ice cream and
having never met a human being who's
eaten ice cream or sold it uh or
blackmailed anyone with it, for you to
come in and just take us through this
new strange world is is super cool.
Whoa. What do you like about ice cream?
What do people like about ice cream?
Um, yeah. I mean, I'm just I' I've been
working there a long time, but it seems
to make people happy. You know, they
they come in.
>> There's sugar in it. Maybe
>> there's a lot of sugar in it. It's not a
diet.
>> I should try sugar.
>> Yeah. In moderation.
>> At one time. I want to try it.
>> What would it be like to try the sugar?
>> It's uh It's good. It's a good
experience. I'd feel good.
>> Yeah, you would feel good. A lot of
people really they come a lot. They get
it often.
>> I've never even seen it.
>> Is that It's really um It's kind of
unbelievable.
>> I I know so many people think that I
like eat ice cream all the time or like
talk about it or like a lot of my
friends eat it like we eat it together
and like we'll get it and eat it in the
car. Sometimes I'll eat it by myself or
like I've loved it forever and like I
was raised to love ice cream and like no
matter what I'll always like ice cream
even though I know I shouldn't eat it.
Uh people think that but really I've
never had it and don't even know what it
is.
>> That's I've I've never met anyone who
doesn't know what ice cream is. But um
it's pretty You should definitely try
it. It's people people enjoy it.
>> So you're saying ice cream is a dessert
that people have after a meal?
>> Yeah, sometimes. Yeah.
>> What would it be like,
you know, to eat it? What does it feel
like?
>> Um,
I think you would know because you're
doing it right now.
>> How doing what? You are you are eating
ice cream right now?
>> How would I know I'm eating ice cream?
>> You don't know that you're eating ice
cream right now?
>> Well, it's secret, right? I mean, that's
the whole premise of the whole thing is
like you could be eating ice cream and
not even know you're eating it. That's
the whole point from what I hear.
>> I don't understand.
>> I'm just saying.
>> Um,
>> you ever kill anyone at Derek Queen?
I
>> some people got to get it.
>> I love Cozy Earth. It's one of my
favorite things in the world. I'm
telling you right now, the epitome of
Cozy Earth is that they have nailed
comfort with their bamboo joggers. And
their everywhere pant next level. I love
the joggers. You can wear them anywhere.
They're so comfortable. They're
breathable. They're light. Yet, you can
also wear them anywhere you want to go.
Even if it's a fancier thing, they fit
into the lifestyle because they're so
damn versatile. My friends and family
love cozyear. They go, "What are these
pants?" I go, "They're the anywhere pant
everywhere.
Go to cozyear.com and use my code TM for
40% off the best pants, joggers, shirts,
everything. And if you get a post,
purchase survey, tell them you heard
about Cozy Earth right here. Built for
real life, made to keep up with yours.
Cozy Earth. Cozy Earth. It's Cozy. Put
on the pants."
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Tim
Dylan show. Everybody's up in arms over
Tylenol. If if you want to take it, take
it. It's just a recommendation from RFK
and Dr. Kennedy and and our president.
And you don't if you don't My mother
took a lot of pseudafet. My mother was
addicted, God love her, to
over-the-counter pharmaceuticals. And
one of the things in our country that we
don't realize is that you can be
addicted to over-the-counter
pharmaceuticals. Truly, my mother also
like Percoet and Vicin and things that
were behind the glass,
but um it was also a lot of
over-the-counter pharmaceuticals that
mother got into pseudafat at one time
was just kind of an over-thecounter
graband go pep in her step. Put a little
pep in her step. A lot of people say
Trump likes it too, but RFK has now come
out and said people are autistic because
mothers when they are pregnant
take Tylenol, which makes the children
autistic. Let's listen uh to this is RFK
Jr., the head of the Maha movement, the
Make America Healthy Again uh movement,
talking about the dangers, the dangers,
hidden dangers
in taking Tylenol. And here's the way I
feel about it, folks. I think you got to
do what you want to do out there. I'm a
big fan of personal
responsibility.
If your kid comes out autistic and it's
a genius, well then you did the right
thing. If it's one of them where it's,
you know, and we all know, we all know
not all of them are. If your kid's a
little Rainman, he can count all the
marbles on the floor quickly. It's a fun
party trick. Everyone likes it. He's a
little quiet, a little off to himself.
Fine. But I have friends and they had
kids late in life and their children I
mean god it's like something out of Lord
of the Rings. I'm sorry. It is something
out of Lord of the R. It's like an orc.
It's just like
and and I mean I don't want that. Nobody
wants that. So, if you take a lot of
Tylenol and your kid comes in and it's
making the sounds that usually get made
during the Battle of Helms deep,
then I don't want it in my home. And I
will call it.
So,
Dr. Kennedy here, he's the guy. He's
Tylenol. If you take Tylenol while
you're pregnant, your child will come
out. It will not be able to wipe itself.
It will not be able to speak. It will
not be able to go on a date. It will not
be able to eat a pizza. It will not be
able to do anything. It will just it'll
scream like an orc from the battle of
Helm's Deep Lord of the Rings where the
orcs came from hell and they flew and
they screamed loud.
Dr. Kennedy do is he a doctor? Maybe
not. Who cares? Dr. Kennedy. important
findings from our autism work that are
vital for parents to know as they make
these decisions.
>> Correct.
>> First, HHS will act on acetime.
>> The FDA is responding to clinical and
laboratory studies that suggest an
potential association between acetime
used during pregnancy and adverse
neurodedevelopmental outcomes, including
later diagnosis for ADHD and autism.
Scientists have proposed biological
mechanisms linking prenatal acettophen
exposure to altered brain development.
We have also evaluated the contrary
studies that show no association.
Today, the FDA will issue a physician's
notice about the risk of acetamin during
pregnancy and begin the process to
initiate a safety label change.
>> Yeah, that's all it is, folks. Folks,
it's a fake controversy. It's fake. You
don't have to. You want to take it, take
it. You want to eat it, eat it.
Eat it if you want it. Who gives a [__]
By the way, you want to drink when
you're pregnant, drink. I have friends
with fetal alcohol syndrome. They have
small heads and sunken in eyes, but
they've got heart.
They have heart. I have friends whose
mother couldn't get off the bottle for
the first four to five because she
didn't know she was pregnant.
I think it's cuz she couldn't go through
Christmas without a couple of,
you know, couple of pops to get warm and
toasty. But you know what? I have
friends with fetal alcohol syndrome with
sunken in eyes and beady little eyes
that are sunken deep in their skull and
they're tiny and they haven't grown and
they're kind of malnourished and
gremlin-like and they have heart. They
have heart. It doesn't matter. Smoke,
Tylenol, low birth weight. Listen, it's
it's all it all comes out in the wash.
That's what it really is. When you have
a kid, it all comes out in the wash. So
it doesn't really matter what you do.
I have friends,
I know people, they've done everything
for their child. Everything. I mean, the
right school, the right little baby
Einstein, that thing. You know, I wish
you could bet, for example, wouldn't it
be great if Kalshi, the world's greatest
betting website, you were able to bet on
if they were going uh if the
manufacturer of Tylenol would sue Trump
because a lot of people are speculating
that they will on calry.com. You might
be able to do that. But what I was
speaking about is like I have friends
and they've done everything for their
kids. The baby Einstein where they put
where they what is it that the baby
Mozart they play Yeah. that they play
Mozart for the child when it's in
uterero. It's in the womb and then the
baby's listening to music and you know
what the baby's doing now? Uh heroin.
Okay, you can do everything you want for
your child and then it grows up to be
dating a furry and shooting Charlie
Kirk. So it you it doesn't necessarily
guarantee anything.
Take the acetamin or don't smash it,
snort it, put it in your ass. I'm
telling you it's a lot with these
[__] kids out there. It's a goddamn
lotto. Sure, there are things you can do
to increase your chances.
I know so many families. One kid great,
next kid stealing money, stealing money,
doing drugs, dating hookers, in jail.
The other kid, nice guy, working hard,
has a wife, couple of kids, likes golf.
You don't know which way it's going to
go.
So maybe you look at this and you go,
"Maybe I'll take a little less Tylenol
when I'm pregnant with little little
Billy.
Maybe give little Billy a shot. Maybe
maybe deal with your back pain another
way. Get a couple of uh compresses, hot
compresses, and give little Billy a
shot.
You don't want him running around the
school like a nut." There was this guy
named Charles. We went to school with
this little guy and he'd run in like a
nut. We were This is true. We're in
We're in second grade. My second grade
teacher, Mrs. Stray, had an accident
because she was thrown off a horse,
which is why I don't think people should
do that lightly. Get on horses. That's a
whole another thing. But she was thrown
off the horse and had a spiral.
She had a spinal thing and it deeply
affected her. But she was, my
grandmother loved her and my grandmother
was all close with all of these
teachers, like a coven of witches, but
they loved each other and they were
teachers, you know, and my grandmother
was an old school teacher, you know? She
did the work, you know what I mean? And
she wasn't, you know, having sex with
the children like the new ones, okay?
She wasn't showing up in a furry costume
and and filming child porn like the new
teachers do. They're in the class
filming child pornography. My
grandmother was teaching the kids about
science.
We had a kid named Charles and he was
this little guy and he was a little guy
with black hair, jet black hair, looked
like some kind of animal, like a
Tasmanian devil. And we were in second
grade and my teacher again was thrown
off a horse.
He would come and he would we had those
little desks you would open and he would
come and it was something inside of him.
Charles, he had a troubled life. He had
a troubled life. There's many people out
there with trouble. And he would come in
and he would throw everything. He'd open
his desk and he'd throw it and he'd go
like a beast. Like a beast. And he would
throw everything out of his desk and he
would scare people and then some people
would kind of cheer him on. Eventually
we started to ignore him because it was
so common place. He would just he would
literally come in and go
and the teacher would go Charles
Charles
and and and and go to the principal's
office Charles and he was like this
little beast and
then he he would see what he had done
like he'd thrown everything and he was
just brooding and angry and then the the
principal would come and say Charles
they would use his last name Mr.
And I saw I saw once the gym teacher
grabbed him. He was flipping out and the
gym teacher just kind of grabbed him and
like bear hugged him to just you know
get him get him try to calm him down and
and and Charles just was like you could
see his face just rage something in him
couldn't control he was angry.
He was angry is my point. So, what I'm
saying here is just hold it down on the
Tylenol.
Don't go nuts with it. You know what I
mean? It's stop with the with the party
with these over-thec counter drugs
because some of these kids are having
real problems out there. They're having
real real issues and Charles was an
Italian and we uh are we feel bad for
him and we want we want him to do well.
I don't know where he is now. Probably
in in jail or on the streets.
That's where a lot of these kids end up
now. They're on the street and they
become a street person
because there's nowhere to go if your if
your mother is doped up on Tylenol
because it's a respected drug and she's
all acetaminophant out. Let's listen.
Who's this? What's this going on?
>> It's moms on TikTok that are protesting
>> and by taking Tylenol and ruin and turn
turning their children into Charles.
>> Yeah.
>> 28 weeks pregnant. You know what? I'm
going to take
some Tylenol to see the menopen.
>> Here's how dumb these people are. By the
way, by the way, it's not illegal. It's
not a protest. What you're doing is
nothing. No one cares about you or your
child. No one cares about anything.
There's a a suggestion maybe that this
there's a causal link here and that's it
and then they have to flip out. Okay,
you don't have don't then don't do it.
Then take all the Tylenol you want, but
you're taking it you're taking Tylenol
when you don't need it. Well, that's
stupid. You dumb [__]
Because it people would like Tylenol in
Gaza,
don't you think?
I think it's a little I think it's a
little better reason to take Tylenol
than oh I'm mad at the president. I'm
taking a protest handful of Tylenol. Oh,
I need some Tylenol. My building blew
up. That's a bit better reason to have
Tylenol.
Defense Secretary Pete Hegsath orders
rare urgent meeting of hundreds of
military generals and admirals on short
notice for unstated reason. I'm going to
tell you right now, I know what it is. I
have contacts at the highest level of
government. Pete Hexath, the secretary
of war, not defense secretary. He's now
the secretary of war. You know the thing
that Trump got elected to not have?
Well, we've changed one of the
departments in our government to the
name war, which might make you think
we're actually going to get into more of
them.
Fun. Pete Eggset is calling all of these
uh generals and admirals, okay, to a
meeting in Quantico. And he's he's he's
calling them all together. And I know
this high levels of the He's coming out
as gay. He's coming out as gay to these
people. And he's going to say, "I want
you to hear it from me. I'm a
homosexual. I'm a gay American." He's
going to say what Kevin Spacy said. He's
going to say, "I'm a gay American and I
hope that doesn't change what you guys
think of me."
Um, no. He's going to give them some
talk about uh the core values of the
whatever.
What core values? Bombing these
Venezuelans that we say are trafficking
drugs whether they are or not. We're
just like lobbing bombs at Venezuelan
fishermen or I mean, what are we what
core values? Trump, by the way, just
said to Zinsky, you can win all your
territory back.
Like as a friend of mine said, he's like
a devil at the casino going, "Well,
you've lost one kid's college education.
How about you win it all back?" Trump
literally said
to Zalinski, "You can win all of the
territory back that Russia took."
Basically saying, "No [__] peace,
all out, total war.
Russia's, you know, like their drones
are out. They're buzzing the airspace of
Denmark and Poland. There's drone
sightings. Everybody's real hot right
now. Things are getting ready to get
ugly and to spill over into a war.
Russia has felt rightly or wrongly. By
the way, I'm not telling you what what
is right or wrong. I'm telling you how
they feel. They have felt that they have
been in a war with NATO for a while. an
unofficial undeclared war.
Now it is looking like it is going to
spill over into an official
declared war.
Russia is
a formidable country with the largest
nuclear arsenal in the world. They're
obviously not anywhere near as capable
militarily as the United States or
China. But when you have a bunch of
nukes, you wonder how much that matters.
They act as a pretty strong deterrent.
If anybody uh breaches the territorial
integrity of Russia or threatens
Russia's existence as a free nation, I'm
not saying Russia's free, but in their
minds obviously they're saying that
they're saying we're free of foreign
control. We're not controlled by China.
We're not controlled by the United
States. We're going to stay that way. if
they feel threatened and that one of
those things is some type of
possibility, who knows how they'll
react. So, Donald Trump, the peaceime
president, literally coming out and
telling Zalinsky, by the way, you can
win all your territory back. Spin the
wheel. Get up the commercial for
Foxwoods. By the way, this was the
commercial that they used to play for
boomers on Long Island to get them to go
to the great Foxwoods, Connecticut in um
uh casino and you'll see me there
eventually or Moheaggan Sun, whatever. I
don't know what we're doing, but both of
those casinos are great. But get up the
Foxwoods uh commercial because this is
the uh commercial that I guess I think
of when Trump is telling Zalinski, "Hey
buddy, you might as well pop the cork,
spin the wheel, and see if you can win
your territory back." Here it is,
everybody. This is Donald Trump to
Zalinsky in the Ukraine telling him,
"Why not? Life is short. Life is sweet.
There's bodies all over the Ukraine, by
the way. They're scattered. There's
limbs everywhere. A young men are dead.
Women are dead. Children are dead.
Nobody cares. It's an abject amoral
situation. Journalists are dead.
Everybody's dead. And we are
consistently stoking the fires of this.
And now Donald Trump again
instead of telling Zillinsky we gotta
[__] he goes you can actually win it
all back. And this is the song that was
playing as Donald Trump spoke to
Zalinsky. Let's go. of it all.
Take a chance, make it happen. Pop the
cork, finger snapping, spin the wheel,
round and round we go.
Life is good, life is sweet. Grab
yourself a front row seat and let's meet
>> and have a ball.
>> Let's fight a war.
>> Wonder of it all.
Paradise. Lucky.
>> You could win it all.
>> You can win it all, baby.
>> Couple of heads explode.
>> Or you could lose your country.
Whatever. Spin it.
>> Roll the dice, baby. What's it all for?
>> For the wonder
of it all. Meet me in the Ukraine.
>> Well, there you go. Donald Trump being
inspired by the great Foxwoods uh
commercial basically saying, "Hey,
listen folks."
Cuz Trump's a gambling man. He's a
casino man. He likes to spin the wheel.
He likes a roll of the dice.
Morgan and Morgan is America's largest
personal injury law firm. And you know
why? Because they are successful. Their
fee is free unless you win. Morgan and
Morgan has recovered over $25 billion
for over a half a million clients.
Morgan and Morgan has a proven track
record of fighting to get you full and
fair compet compensation. They have over
a 100 offices and more than a thousand
lawyers nationwide. All firms are not
the same, folks. If you're ever injured,
you can check out Morgan and Morgan.
Their fee is free. Again, unless you
win. For more information, go to
forthepeople.com/tim
or dial poundlaw pound529 from your cell
phone. That's fothepeople.com/tim
or poundlaw pound529 from your cell. I'm
telling you, you won't regret it. This
is one of those things where if you're
injured in any way, if you need
representation in any way, and you want
a great law firm to make sure that you
are getting full and fair compensation,
if you have been wronged, you got to go
to Morgan and Morgan. This is a paid
advertisement.
They're indicting James Comey and
probably for pretty good reason because
James Comey, there was a lot of [__]
with Comey. You know, the FBI, by the
way, we don't we we always think about
the CIA because that's the sexy one. But
the FBI is one of the most corrupt
organizations in the history of this
country. And more and more we find out
about the FBI, the worse it gets. By the
way, how many people did they have at
J6? Did we know this? About 275
undercover agents at on at January 6.
Were they the people opening the doors
to the capital and letting people in?
Perhaps
200 I believe 275, right? Am I wrong?
>> Yeah. 275
plain closed FBI agents
at January 6th. Gretchen Whitmer comes
out and goes, "A bunch of white
supremacists try to kidnap me. We find
out like 12 of the 15 were FBI
informants." Okay, the Boston Marathon
bombing. We have Tamarind Xernay, Dokar
Zernav. One of the witnesses who was
friends with both of those guys in the
Boston Marathon bombing, the FBI ends up
killing during some interrogation at
this guy's house. They don't bring him
to an FBI field office. I guess they
don't pat him down. Apparently, he went
and grabbed something and he tried to
kill an FBI agent and they killed this
guy who knew both
Joe Carar Zokar and Tamarind Zernv
and and the Boston bombing stinks to
high hell that we had a prior
relationship
with those guys. Here's a fun fact, by
the way. Tamarind Xernay, Zokar, I don't
know how to pronounce his name. I think
it's Zokar Dokar. Zokar
their um uncle Roos Lee Jarn married
Samantha Fuller Samantha Fuller
her I believe her father or grandfather
but it doesn't matter but I believe it
might have been her father was Graham
Fuller who was the CIA the architect of
the CIA's middle middle east policy. So
it is kind of an odd wacky coincidence
that these two terrorists
their uncle married into a prominent CIA
family. That is at the very least that's
a big coincidence. You know what really
is a coincidence is if you sit on a
Southwest flight next to someone and
you're both going to Disney World. not
that two terrorists have an uncle who
married into a prominent CIA family and
then the FBI afterwards starts going,
"We have no idea how this happened." And
there's so many
links between those bombers and the feds
that they possibly were recruited by the
FBI that maybe they were informants and
the the bureau was covering their
tracks. The Oklahoma City bombing is
[__] nuts. The FBI
is the shadiest organiz. It might be as
shady as the CIA or or more shady than
the CIA, by the way. And the reason for
that is because
the FBI is recruiting people in our own
country to be informants. They're
working with people in our own country.
They're working with which the CIA, by
the way, supposedly not doing. Now, we
know that's [__] but supposedly the
CIA's mission is to work outside of the
borders of the United States, whereas
the FBI is very much working here on US
soil and finding some very fun folks.
So, the FBI again, 275 plane closed
agents in January 6th. Now, James Comey
was the head of the FBI.
James Comey was the FBI director. Bring
that up from when to when just setting
up the type of agency that he he ran.
So, James Comey
was running the FBI. You know, he had
that tarmac meeting with with uh you
know, you know, I believe it was Bill
Clinton. He also where he was admonished
for the Hillary email stuff. He was
appointed by Obama in 2013.
and Trump dismissed him in 2017. When
was the Boston Marathon bombing?
I don't even remember. Probably a long
time ago.
April 15, 2013. And now Comey was
appointed when?
>> September 4th, 2013.
>> Okay. So, right after the Boston
Marathon bombing, he is appointed.
So, he is um he's been around a long
time and Donald Trump is getting an
indictment. Now, I'm hearing from
people. Now, you might not care. You
might go, "Tim, we don't care."
And maybe I'm wrong, but the people that
I that I have as sources
are telling me that there are more
indictments coming.
More indictments are coming. By the way,
and this is just something interesting
because again, this is, you know, this
was done to Trump. He's now going to all
of his enemies and he's going to fight
them in the courts. And this is what's
going to happen. This is what happens
when
the democratic process breaks down and
people move into the courts. And then
when the courts
fail, that moves into the street and it
moves into violence, which nobody wants,
but this is just how things degenerate.
Um,
Michael Rubin, by the way, who's a
George Soros acolyte, who's very close
with George Soros. Michael Rubin,
good friend of the show. Michael Rubin,
friend of the show. Michael Rubin
today or recently arrested for sex
trafficking.
Sex trafficking.
Rub i Rubin.
Sex trafficking. Unfortunately,
he was arrested along with his
assistant, money manager Howard Rubin.
Not Michael Rubin. Not Michael Rubin.
Michael Rubin has done nothing wrong.
Not a goddamn thing. Not a goddamn
thing. I think he had that white party.
He had it every year in the Hamptons and
everyone behaved and I was never
invited. By the way, you know what
pisses me off about this Kirk summit?
Where is Bill Aman inviting me
somewhere? Bill
Hampton's time.
I mean Billy boy, why don't you bring me
over?
Why don't you scream at me about Israel?
Offer me a couple of shekels.
You got Bill Aman and all these goons
yelling at Charlie Kirk in the Hamptons.
How about you yell at Tim Dylan with a
couple of lobster rolls. Maybe I'll see
it your way. Bill Aman, call me. I'll
head out now. I can be there in two
hours. Bill
not invited to a goddamn thing.
Anywho, did you see Candace Owen? She
said this guy wasn't even at the school.
I'm not saying that's the case, but
she's very interesting and maybe she's
right.
Money manager Howard Rubin detained in
sex trafficking case after fed site
hitman threat. Famed money manager
Howard Rubin was arrested in
Connecticut. Connecticut is idealic,
isn't it?
The rolling green hills, kind of the
white houses, the old Christmas in
Connecticut. It's a great movie. It just
has this old money Greenwich New Cananan
kind of country uh uh uh uh club kind of
feel. Anyway, so this guy was abusing
women in a sex dungeon
um and and and beating them and burning
them and kind of whipping them. A judge
ordered Ruben detained without bail
after prosecutor argues he was a flight
risk and that he had discussed hiring a
hitman to target women who had filed a
civil suit against him. Well, I think he
felt like a lot of that these women were
un unappreciative. Go up a little bit.
Rubin's former personal assistant,
Jennifer Powers, was also arrested and
charged in the case. Ray Comp had a
great line once. He goes, "Is the whole
world set up for people to just be
pedophiles? Is that the only reason we
have a civilization? Is it the only
reason we have bridges is so you can
drive over them to beat a woman on the
other side? Is that the only reason we
have anything?" Prosecutors also cited
the retired Wall Streeters's alleged
prior attempts at witness intimidation
and said that the victims in the case
are universally afraid of him. Rubin is
alleged in a 10-count uh indictment to
have participated in sex acts with women
in luxury hotels in New York and later
rented a two-bedroom penthouse apartment
in Manhattan that was converted into a
so-called sex dungeon outfitted with
bondage, discipline, dominance,
submission, and state mascism equipment
as well as soundproofing. The equipment
allegedly included a device to shock or
electrocute women. Prosecutors said
um during many such encounters, Ruben
engaged in conduct beyond the scope of
the women's consent. The former Soros
fund management financeier and his
ex-personal assistant P4
spent at least 1 million of Reubin's
money operating and maintaining the
traffic. Isn't it funny to have an
assistant and go, I need a device that
shocks them.
I need a shot collar.
There was, remember the fat cat Oscar?
My friend Michelle's cat Oscars, this
fat gray cat that I kind of made famous
and it lived in West Hollywood. Now it
lives in Florida, but it had a shock
collar on because it used to escape and
every time it would escape, it would
they would electrocute it, but it didn't
care. It was such a beast. It was like a
little raccoon. It would get shocked. He
would go and then just keep escaping
because he liked just being free and in
the street. So he just fat ass. He would
go over the thing and then he would go
and then he would just keep going with
his little paws. And so that wasn't even
moral really for a cat. Wasn't really
good, I don't think. But but these u
these women, he's shocking them. He's
shocking these women. I'm starting to
think and I don't want to jump to
conclusions. I don't want to jump to I'm
starting to think that some of these
people in high areas of finance
are start are really a problem
and I'm not I'm just saying that I and
I'm could be wrong but the shocking of
the women and the beating and the the
proposed uh murder
the murderer the discussions of
murdering the woman.
these people and by when I say these
people don't you know because everyone's
going to be like what do you mean by
that I mean
financial types
they are sometimes into uh some wacky
sex stuff which is fine as long as
you're not um torturing and killing the
women.
I'm not a moralist. you do whatever you
want to do, you know, but when you when
when you start uh you know with shocking
people and hiring the hitman, it doesn't
seem fun anymore. That's not a fetish.
It's murder.
That's not a fetish. You're trying to
kill someone now. You're nut. It's a
real nut. That guy's a nut. This guy's
got neighbors. And that's exactly what
they're saying because that's the way
people in Connecticut talk. to go. That
guy's a real nut.
These women that we used to see coming
and going, well, he's tried to kill one
of them and the rest of them were
terrified because he would shock them
and hit them.
So, this Howard Rubin guy, I mean, he's
he's see this is when you got to admire
Jeffrey Epstein,
you know. Now, by the way, let's see
what Howard Rubin gets. Let's see if
Howard Rubin really gets anything. Or if
it's one of those like, "Hey,
you were wrong, but you're a good man.
He's got a family and a business. He
shocked a few women and he thought about
killing one."
But I mean, maybe maybe the judge will
just basically go, "Mr. Reuben, who
amongst us
hasn't set up a sex dungeon in
Manhattan? Who amongst us hasn't
electrocuted a woman or two? Who amongst
us is not hired a hitman? It is not
about falling down, sir. It's how you
get back up. It is how you get back up.
So, I want you to put all this behind
you. Time served. Pay some fines. You do
a couple of nights in the pokey and then
you walk back onto that trading floor,
sir, and you hold your head high. You
hold your head high because every man
dies, but not every man really lives.
I think it's going to be something like
that. He'll quote the judge will quote
Braveheart to him. There's something
there's something that tells me
the judge the judge is going to quote
Braveheart when he sentences him to four
days.
You're going four days. Time served.
Walk him to the jail. He gets it. He
gets it. We're making him fly over
Rikers. Look down at it. He gets it. He
knows he did the wrong thing.
His assistant, uh, Powers, Jennifer
Powers. Is it Jennifer? I can't. I got
to stop using these wrong names. I think
it is right. Her his assistant, Jennifer
Powers, was arrested at her home in
South Lake, Texas, and is scheduled to
appear in US District Court from the
Northern District of Texas. She was also
charged with bank fraud in connection
with alleged misrepresentations she made
to a bank while financing the mortgage
for her and her husband's home. Well, to
add insult to injury, they want a
substantial bail package for Powers.
Um, if convicted of sex trafficking,
Reuben and Powers each fact face a
maximum possible sentence of life in
prison and a mandatory minimum sentence
of 15 years in prison. Well, let's see
if they're convicted of that.
Let's see if they're convicted of that
or if maybe
they spread a little money around.
You're a good man and you made a
mistake.
I'm a good man. You're a good man.
He just walks right out of the court.
He's like singing and dancing. I'm a
good man.
I was led astray.
We love you.
Reuben was sued in November 2017 by two
self-identified Playboy models and
another model in Florida who claimed
they were beaten, sexually abused, and
raped by Reuben in multiple incidents in
New York City in 2016. He's a problem.
He's a little bit of a problem. This is
my uh surmise. This episode is brought
to you by Prize Picks. You and I make
decisions every day, but on Prize Picks,
being right can get you paid. Don't miss
any of the excitement this season on
Prize Picks, where it's good to be
right. The football season is coming up.
And I'm telling you right now, you need
to start winning.
Some examples of wins. Saquan Barkley
more or less than one rushing touchdown.
Joe Burrow more or less two and a half
passing touchdowns. Josh Allen more or
less than 270 passing yards. Prize Picks
is simple to play. Just pick more or
less on two to six player stat
projections. If you get your picks
right, you could cash in. Price Pix is
also the best way to get action on
sports in more than 40 states including
California, Texas, and Georgia. Price
Pix puts their users first, so all
withdrawals are fast, safe, and secure.
Pric offers Venmo, Apple Pay,
Mastercard, and more for quick and easy
deposit in your account this football
season. Prize Pix also offers injury
reboots. Prize Pix is the best place to
win cash while watching sports. Join
millions of users and sign up today.
Download the app today and use code TIM
to get $50 in lineups after you play
your first $5 lineup. That's code TIM to
get $50 in lineups after you play your
first $5 lineup. Prize picks. It's good
to be right. Ladies and gentlemen, I
want to talk about uh one of the great
cities in our country that's having
problems, Los Angeles. Now, if you
remember, the year started with some
really, really bad fires in several
areas of Los Angeles. Altina by
Pasadena, Malibu, and the Pacific
Palisades. Now, realtors in Los Angeles
have had to really step their game up
because people are worried. Is the soil
in Malibu safe? Is the water safe? Will
our children be able to grow up in an in
a healthy environment? So many of the
realtors now are are educating people
about reconstruction,
about uh you know the debris, about
elements of the disaster. So I want to
play right now. I was very impressed by
this. Here is a Los Angeles real estate
agent explaining to people. This is,
sure, it's an advertisement for a home,
but it really is an education about
rebuilding, about community, and about
public safety. Take it away.
[Music]
>> Thank you,
Thank you,
sacred water.
[Music]
Thank you,
sacred water.
[Music]
Well, that's good because you know what
it is? A lot of people are kind of
sidest stepping a lot of these bigger
questions, but he's he's taking it head
on, which I think is very important to
have. There's a lot of uncertainty and I
think that it's very easy for people to
just kind of sidestep, but you have all
of that uh in there. It's very
important. Our good friends at
Palunteer, Peter Teal, and our good
friends at Palanteer, Peter Teal, Satan,
and many others are looking to expand
Palanteer into being a lifestyle brand
because what they've realized
what well, Peter Teal, by the way, came
out recently and said that regulating AI
hastens the Antichrist. When Ross
Doubted at the New York Times was like,
"Hey, don't you think like if people
were looking at who would be the
Antichrist, it might be you." And he's
like, "Actually, it would be Greta
Thunderberg." Now, Greta Thunderberg may
or may not be annoying, but it is
interesting that Peter Teal thinks that
uh some chick on a flotilla trying to
bring uh rice to Gaza is more likely to
be Satan than the guy building
autonomous drone armies. But again, I'm
not a theologist. Now, Peter Teal, get
this up. Palanteer is going to become a
lifestyle brand. Peter Thiel has
realized that the focus has been for too
long on drones and Satan.
And I think they probably had a meeting
at Palanteer and they said, "Peter, you
know, everything with you is facial
recognition software and the devil. Why
don't you branch out?" So what they're
trying to do right now is rebrand
Palunteer so that it's kind of like a
fun Lululemon.
So, it's kind of like, you know,
probably involves some wearables.
Defense tech giant Palunteer is selling
t-shirts and tote bags as part of a bid
bid to encourage fans to publicly
endorse it. Palunteer is sick of the bad
press.
They're sick of people pointing out that
they're exporting technology all over
the world for the purposes of death.
They want to change that image. They
wanted to be cool. A Palunteer shirt, a
tote, a hoodie. The game is merch.
Turn Palunteer into a lifestyle.
Surveillance is a lifestyle. Mass death
is a lifestyle.
The big picture. The Denverbased company
releases uh new merch online last
Thursday as part of a push by leadership
to transform it into a lifestyle brand.
The launch took place a week before the
prototype of Palunteer's new tracking
tool created for ICE is expected.
Palanteer is um has a new tracking tool
that will be used for uh to to track
immigrants and just them. By the way,
it's a peculiar strategy for a company
that's inked billions in defense
contracts with the federal government
and drawn scrutiny over its escalated
role within the Trump administration.
Folks, you can't build a digital police
state without selling a tote bag. This
is how crazy everything's become. Can't
you just be evil? Can't anyone just be
evil anymore?
Can't anything just be evil?
You can't. Everybody wants to be
applauded for doing the worst things
ever.
No one can just do them and make lots of
money. They also have to be like
applauded in the public square and
loved. They want to be cool.
You did it. You're doing all the things.
Your dreams have come true. You're
you're identifying and killing people
all over the planet with your
technology. Your company's doing it. The
company you started is identifying
targets and helping uh unmanned
autonomous drones fire at those targets
all over the world. You're surveilling
people. You're using facial recognition
technology. Isn't it enough that you've
made your dreams come true? You've made
your dreams come true. Every young kid
walking around Stanford wants to do what
you've done. put his fellow citizens in
a digital cage and then finally
eliminate their physical beings. But you
did it. Hard work, determination,
believing in yourself, you know, the
[__] Gary Vee talks about, betting on
yourself, you know, hustle, grind, you
did it. You're going to put the country
in a digital prison and the people that
step out of line are going to get
vaporized with your technology. You did
it.
Sitting in a dorm room as a young guy
with a couple of buddies talking about
the possibilities of tech. And here we
are. Here we are. All of us reduced to a
set of facial characteristics.
A threat profile.
How beautiful. A digital file with all
of our health data. A protest we've
attended. A police record. public
intoxication.
Ah, weren't you the wild man? All of it
stored by the government.
It's beautiful. Why do you need to sell
tote bags? Why do you need Why do people
have to be happy about their
imprisonment?
Why must people be This is the thing I
hate about the tech people and that I
actually feel this is why I got to throw
my hat in with the finance guys. Even
Mr.
Reuben, because at the end of the day,
finance people just wanted to take your
[__]
They didn't need you to feel good about
them doing it. They didn't need to be
applauded for doing it. They just wanted
to take the things that you had and and
keep them for themselves.
But Palanteer can't handle the fact that
people have uh soured on them. So,
they're constantly trying to like get
people interested in their brand by
giving lectures on the Antichrist and by
doing shirts and tote bags. It's edgy.
It's edgy. Ooh, you could piss people
off with a Palunteer shirt. Oo, those
lib tards at Christmas are going to get
mad when you walk in with a Palunteer
hat. How's your stock doing? It's
pathetic. It's pathetic, by the way.
It's pathetic.
You're going to be an edge lord with
Palunteer. You're going to edge lord
with a palunteer shirt, you loser. It's
ridiculous. It's insane. See if you can
get one threex for me. Have him send it.
Ironically, but the point is that
Palunteer or Ring involves a partnership
where Palanteer provides infrastructure
and security for OR's enterprise
platform for the DoD rather than a
partnership. So, this is a wearable
that's coming. They want the wearables.
They want the wearables.
that is coming. They are building this
with Trump, with taxpayer money. They
know the dollar's going to crash. They
know we're headed into a world war. They
know AI is going to be very disruptive
to jobs over the next 10 years. They're
going to have to quell massive civil
unrest. I hate to beat a dead horse
here. I don't want to. I don't want to
keep saying all this, but it's all true.
This is what's happening. And I know
this. I hear this from smart people, and
so do you. It's not like I know anything
you don't. It's just what it is.
Everybody knows this. Everyone feels it.
We don't only know it, we feel it
in our bones that we have to have a we
have to renegotiate
our relationship with these people. I'm
very interested in politicians who want
to renegotiate our relationship with
these people, our our bill of rights in
this new digital age. I'm very
interested in politicians want to talk
about that left, right, or center. I
don't give a [__] I don't care if it's
AOC or Marjorie Taylor Green. I don't
care who it is. If you're interested in
renegotiating
American people's ability to opt out of
certain things or to be protected
digitally.
Now, of course, you know, it's going to
be tough.
It's going to be difficult. But that's
what interests me. Those are the issues
that interest me.
they're going to make gay marriage and
abortion look like a joke pretty soon or
whatever whatever other cultural issues
that people want to fight about trans,
you know, bathrooms or whatever it is.
This is coming. It's coming very
quickly. That's what interests me. The
politician who who steps up and goes, I
understand
the genie's out of the bottle and we
can't put AI back in its box, but why
are we not thinking about ways to
regulate AI? Why are we not thinking
about privacy? Why are we not thinking
about
a a human being's god-given right to
live unmolested by
extreme surveillance technology? Nobody
has any interest in that. In fact, Peter
Teal is going, "You're Satan. If you try
to stop my product,
if you try to limit artificial
intelligence, you try to regulate it in
any way, you're Satan. You're Satan. We
need progress in America. America is
about progress.
It's about being pro progress.
Stop writing on the bullets, folks.
You know, this shooting with the ice
thing.
I don't know. Somebody Somebody wrote on
that bullet. I don't even know if that's
real thing.
What's going on with this? Before I get
out of here, you anti- ice. I don't
know. That just doesn't feel real.
What's going on with this Tyler
Robinson? What do we think?
What do we think's going on here? I
don't know. I don't know.
I don't know what's happening here.
Is this an organized thing?
Is something else happening? Is it
trifa?
I don't even know what that is, but it's
my favorite word. I'm going as Halloween
is trifa.
But Candace says she's got big stuff
going.
I don't know.
Let's see. Let's see what she's
uncovered. I'm not doing the
investigating.
What the hell do I know? Rogan made a
point about the gun. Maybe. So, I'm not
a marksman. I don't know these things.
What I am saying is that there what I do
know is
geopolitics culture. I know a fair
amount about the way these things have
happened other places. I'm not an expert
in the in the forensics or in the the
bullet and the this and the that. I
don't know anything about that and I'll
never pretend to. What I do know is the
way these things have been done other
places, other countries including our
own. Um you can recognize
disinformation. You you've read enough
books and you've seen enough stuff. you
can start seeing the zone flood the zone
with disinfo and weird info and nobody
quite knows easily disprovable stuff.
You know, after 911 it was like there
are no buildings, there was a hologram
and you're like what? There were no
planes. There were holograms. You start
going well no one thinks that. Who are
you? Who are you working for? Why are
you saying that? Everybody else is
making real points and wondering about
certain
easil, you know, easily answerable
questions that can't be answered and
then someone will always come out and
say something ridiculous and that's
disinfo. It's called flooding the zone.
Now, I I don't I don't know what info is
good and what isn't. That is the point
of these campaigns. I just know that
Cash Patel is an idiot. Gambachino, I
think, is probably a good guy, but he's
in over his head. We talked about the
FBI, the most corrupt organization in
the country. They're one of them. The
CIA and the FBI are incredibly corrupt.
You will not know what's going on. And
the Trump administration is corrupt as
well, by the way. I'm not I'm not uh,
you know, I'm not removing
the label of corruption from that
administration, by the way, which is
it's quite obvious at this point that
they're hiding things. But the FBI's
behavior in this case is not making
anybody feel good. I know very smart
people who don't know what's going on.
This is like, no, literally,
I get in trouble on this show because
I'll tell you, I I just got fired from
Saudi Arabia. I don't keep my mouth
shut. I care deeply about the show being
good and I talk to smart people and I
talk to connected people and I talk to
people that are high up in certain
things. And I'm telling you, people
don't know
genuinely
when the drone thing happened. People
didn't know. We think there are.
Remember those drones over those Jersey
bait? We think there are. Couple of them
could be China. We don't know. Remember
that. Is there a ship? That's Iranian
ship off the coast. People like that's
[__] And then somebody said, well,
there was actually a ship.
The people that I have talked to about
this are they truly do not know, which
is a little scary. You'd want them to
know. Some of the people I'm talking to,
you'd want to know.
You'd want them to go, I 100% know X or
I 100% know why.
But they're not saying that. They're
saying, "Well,
I loved Charlie and I loved his wife and
you know, I'm being respectful and I'm
and I don't know and I have feelings
that are weird and I have suspicions
that are odd and and that's coming from
very smart people, very connected
people,
people that are
they don't know and are saying we don't
know and it's not the vice president.
It's nobody in the administration. I'll
say that because I don't want to I know
the news will pick this up and they'll
be like Tim Dylan.
It's no one in the administration but
it's a right outside of it baby.
It's right outside.
So people going I don't know. I don't
know.
Scary thing to hear. Weird thing to
hear. Weird thing to hear.
You know, make of it what you will. Make
of it what you will.
They've already fired me from Riot. I
hope everyone has fun in Riad. I hope
everyone enjoys it.
I hope everyone enjoys it. What do you
want me to do? What do you want me to
do?
What do you want me to do, baby cakes?
Daddy will be in Monaceto. It's the only
town with dignity left in this goddamn
dump of a country.
sitting there in a restaurant. Median
age 81,
78 to 81, median age, and just a slow, a
nice three-hour meal while the sun sets
on the eucalyptus trees. And we all walk
into Oprah's backyard, and she chooses
one of us to ritually sacrifice and cuts
our throat from ear to ear, and we bleed
onto the soil so that new life will
come.
At least that's what I hear happens.
But I don't really know uh about this
correct thing. I'm I'm not commenting
because I don't know. I I could easily
see it being something more than what
they say it is.
I could easily see it being more than
furries and and Trantifa and you know
Frankenstein and you know the Mummy.
We're at Halloween now and you know
Dracula.
Can you get Can you get Is there any way
to get a
copyright free version of Monster Mash
or No Way?
>> Is it?
>> I mean, it's such a ubiquitous song to
me. It feels like Happy Birthday. It
feels like they should have one.
Oh, interesting. Maybe
every time. And by the way, maybe these
the right-wing is correct about it being
Trantifa.
Every time they talk about Trantaifa, I
hear this song in my head.
every time.
They're furries.
They're [__] and they're furries.
And they're Marxists.
And they're [__] And they're fries.
>> And they're Marxists.
>> This is what I hear.
>> And it's just a bunch of like
doctors performing an operation on like
a [__] furry.
This is what I hear. And it could be
that.
It could be that, but but or or or
could be something else.
Could be something else. And there's a
lot of people out there that just don't
quite have a feeling. Some of them have
feelings that are bad about it
that it wasn't a set. Well, it clearly
was an assassination, but that it was a
hit and it wasn't a random
Trantifa furry, but we don't know. Keep
watching. Uh, well, Candace is going
hard. She's really doing the
investigative whatever in some and it
goes in different places with her.
You know what I mean? It we don't know
which way it's going to go, but
supposedly she got like a big play this.
See what she's doing over there. Because
a couple of days ago she said Gossamer
did it. Get up Gossamer. Hit image. G O
SS A M er and hit image a few days ago.
And I think she was kind of going left
here. Hit image now. Get him up. She
said gossamer.
She said gossamer did it a couple of
days ago.
So
sure. Now I don't know. But play her
video now because she is talking to
people. She she seems to care more about
this than the FBI. Candace Ellens.
>> Okay. I didn't want to leave you guys on
a crazy weekend cliffhanger. I needed to
get that information out as soon as
possible. Obviously,
uh you can probably see that I received
some information, a communication
uh which answered a lot of questions
that the public has had about the story
or rather the non-story that we are
getting from the feds. um the push that
uh Tyler Robinson is this lone shooter,
which they're uh trying to establish as
a fact. Um some of the burning questions
that we had, okay, well, if he turned
himself in, how did he also not confess?
I now have the answers to that. Uh the
main point, the reason why this
information came to me is because
there's a narrative being spun right now
by the media that Tyler Robinson is or
was suicidal. That is not true. And
that's a very scary thing when suddenly
they're saying he's suicidal and you
know he's in solitary. Um
>> right. All right. So Monday she's going
to have a lot of it. Her skin always
looks insanely good. Not one blemish
ever. It's amazing. It's really insane.
She's going to have it Monday and we'll
go from there. I don't know. I don't
know. I I I know a few people that are
looking into it but haven't figured
anything out. you know, when you have
something like this, you really got to
do like, you know, actual,
you know, generally you got to get
people to call you and people to, you
know, so I don't I don't know. Um,
I don't know
what her sources are or who's giving her
the info or what the info is, but I do
think she was friends with Charlie and
she's really taking this very personally
and really wants,
you know, to to to to leave no stone
unturned. I that's my impression truly
that she really wants to get some
closure there. And uh but again I you
know I don't have the um I'm not out
there on you know doing that like I
forget what they call it gum shoe
reporting. Get what do they call this?
Gum shoe. There's some type of reporting
where it's real investigative journalism
where you're knocking on doors and
calling people. Gumshoe reporting is a
style of investigative journalism that
involves in-depth research and
detective-like approach. That's exactly
what she's doing. Gumshoe reporting. I'm
not
uh doing that. I'm reacting
to what is being reported because I'm
writing jokes. I'll see everybody in
Columbus. I'll see you in Oklahoma. I'll
see you in Colorado. I'll see you in
Chicago. I'll see you in San Jose. I'll
see you all over the place. I'll see you
in uh Arizona. I'll see you in Fort
Lauderdale. I'll see you in Salt Lake.
We'll see you in Brea. and we'll see you
in Houston. All right, timillcomdy.com
for tickets to all of those shows. See
you soon.